A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Librarian of Virginia, 1832-2024 Jan
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and Subject Files, 1827-2007.
  - 1995 (Accession 41208)., 2 cu. ft. (2 boxes)
    - Agendas and Supporting Documentation, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence with Board Members, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Board Member Personal Correspondence, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Library Advisory Commission, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - State Historical Records Advisory Board, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - State Networking Users Advisory Board, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Invitations, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - American Library Associations, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Chief Officers of State Library Agencies, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Friends of Virginia Libraries, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Richmond Area Museum Directors, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Genealogical Society, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Council for America's First Freedom, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 1996-1998 (Accession 40565)., 3 cu. ft. (3 boxes)
    This collection contains the correspondence of State Librarian, Nolan T. Yelich. Correspondents include but are not limited to; state and federal agencies, associations, and foundations. Topics discussed are; Virginia State Library funding, collections and services. Included are; reports, letters, memorandums, and invitations.
    Arranged alphabetically by folder title, thereunder chronological.
    - Accomplishments Report, 1996-1998. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - American Library Association (ALA), 1996-1998. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Annual Report, 1996-1998. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Archival and Information Services, 1996-1998. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Association of Southestern Research Libraries (ASERL), 1996. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Attorney General, 1996. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Attorney General, 1997-1998. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Board Agendas and Documents, 1996-1998. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Board Member Correspondence, 1996. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Board Member Correspondence, 1997. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Board Member Correspondence, 1998. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Board Member Correspondence - Personal, 1996-1997. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Board Member Correspondence - Personal, 1998. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Board Minutes, 1996-1998. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Celebration 2007 (Jamestown), 1997-1998. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Center for the Book, 1996-1998. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Chief Officers of State Library Agencies (COSLA), 1996-1998. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Collection Management Services Division, 1997-1998. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1998. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Congress, 1996. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Council for America's First Freedom, 1997-1998. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Council on Information Management, 1996-1998. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Dedication - Library of Virginia: Remarks by John W. Carlin, 1997. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Direct Constituent Correspondence, 1996. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Direct Constituent Correspondence, 1997. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Direct Constituent Correspondence, 1998. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Federal Agencies, 1996-1998. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Finance and Administrative Services Division, 1996. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Finance and Administrative Services Division, 1997. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Finance and Administrative Services Division, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Foundation Development Office, 1996-1997. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Foundation Development Office, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Files, 1997-1998. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Friends of Virginia Libraries (FOVL), 1996-1998. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - General Assembly, 1996. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - General Assembly, 1997. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - General Assembly, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - General Services, Department of, 1996-1998. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Governor's Office, 1996. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Governor's Office, 1997. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Governor's Office, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Higher Education Council (SCHEV), 1996-1998. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Information Technology, Department of, 1996-1998. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Institute for Museum and Library Services, 1997-1998. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Invitations, 1996-1998. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Library Advisory Commission, 1996. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Library Board Records, 1997. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Library Development and Networking, 1996. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Library Development and Networking, 1997. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Library Development and Networking, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Library of Congress, 1996-1998. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Library Services and Construction Act (LSCA), 1997. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Locality Correspondence, 1996. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Locality Correspondence, 1997. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Locality Correspondence, 1998. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - National Association of Government Archives and Records Administration (NAGARA), 1996-1997. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - National Association of State Information Resource Executives (NASIRE), 1997-1998. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - National Commission on Libraries and Information Science (NCLIS), 1996-1998. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Old Dominion University Teletechnet, 1996; 1998. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Other States, 1996-1997. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Personnel and Training, Department of, 1996-1998. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Planning and Budget, Department of, 1996-1998. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Publications and Educational Services Division, 1996-1998. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Records Management and Imaging Services Division, 1996-1997. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Records Management and Imaging Services Division, 1998. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Richmond Area Museum Directors, 1996-1998. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Secretary of Education, 1996-1997. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Secretary of Education, 1998. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Sole Source Request, 1997-1998. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - state Agencies - Other, 1996. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - State Agencies - Other, 1997. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - State Agencies - Other, 1998. (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - State Historical Records Advisory Board (SHRAB), 1996-1998. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - State Librarian's Office and Staff, 1996-1998. (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - State Networking Users Advisory Board (SNUAB), 1996-1998. (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - State Public Records Advisory Council (SPRAC), 1996-1998. (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - statement of Economic Interest - Staff, 1996. (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Strategic Management Plan, 1996-1997. (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Strategic Management Plan, 1998. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Southeastern Library Network (SOLINET), 1996-1998. (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Virginia Coalition for Open Government, 1997-1998. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Virginia Genealogical Society, 1997-1998. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Virginia Library Association (VLA), 1998. (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Virginia Library Association (VLA), 1996-1998. (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Virginia Public Library Directors Association (VPLDA), 1996-1998. (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - White House Conference on Library and Information Science Task Force (WHCLIST), 1996-1998. (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - 1999 (Accession 41116)., 2 cu. ft. (2 boxes)
    This collection contains the correspondence of State Librarian, Nolan T. Yelich. Correspondents include but are not limited to; state and federal agencies, libraries, associations, and foundations. Topics discussed are; Virginia State Library funding, collections and services. Included are; reports, letters, memorandums, and invitations.
    - Agendas and Supporting Documentation, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Agendas and Supporting Documentation, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - American Historical Association, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - American Library Association (ALA), 1999. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - ALA, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Archival and Information Services Division, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Association of Southeastern Research Libraries, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Attorney General, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Board Memebers, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Board Memebers Correspondence, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Board Memebers Correspondence - personal, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Celebration 2007, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Center for the Book, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Chief Officers of State Library Agencies, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Collection Management Services Division, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Council for America's First Freedom, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Council on Information Management, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Digital Library, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Direct Constituent Correspondence (A-E), 1999. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Direct Constituent Correspondence (F-Z), 1999. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Education, Secretary of, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Federal Agencies, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Financial and Administrative Services Division, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Gates Foundation, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Gates Foundation, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - General Assembly, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - General Services, Department of, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Governor's Office, 1999. (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Higher Education Council, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Information Technology, Department of, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Information Technology Services Division, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Institute for Museums and Library Services, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Internal Correspondence, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Invitations, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Librar Advisory Commission (SCHEV), 1999. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Library Board Foundation, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Library Development and Networking Division, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Library of Congress, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Locality Correspondence, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - National Association of Government Archives and Records Association (NAGARA), 1999. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - National Association of State Information Resource Executives (NASIRE), 1999. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - National Commission on Libraries and Information Science (NCLIS), 1999. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Old Dominion University (TELETECHNET), 1999. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Personnel and Training, Department of, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Planning and Budget, Department of, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Publications and Educational Services Division, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Records Management and Imaging Services Division, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Richmond Area Museum Directors, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Southeastern Library Network, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - States - other, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - State Agencies - other, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - State Historical Records Advisory Board (SHRAB), 1999. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - State Networking Users Advisory Board (SNUAB), 1999. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Strategic Management Plan, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Coalition for Open Government, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Virginia Cultural Network, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Virginia Genealogical Society, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Virginia Library Association (VLA), 1999. (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Virginia Public Library Directors Association, 1999. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - White House Conference on Library and Information Science Task Force (WHCLIST), 1999. (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - 2000 (Accession 44543)., 1.35 cu. ft. (2 boxes)
    - Agendas and Supporting Documentation, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - American Library Association (ALA), 2000. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Archival and Information Services Division, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Art Museum of Western Virginia, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Association for the Preservation of Virginia Antiquities, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Association of Southeastern Research Libraries (ASERL), 2000. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Attorney General, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Board Handbook, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Board Member Correspondence, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Board Member Correspondence - personal, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Board Minutes, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Celebration 2007 (Jamestown-Yorktown), 2000. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Center for the Book, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Chief Officers of State Library Agencies, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Collections Management Services Division, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Congress, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Council for America's First Freedom, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Council of State Library Agencies in Northeast (COSLINE), 2000. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Council on Information Management, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Digital Library, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Direct Constituent Correspondence, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Education, Secretary of, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Federal Agencies, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Financial Administrative Services Division, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Foundation Development Office, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Friends of Virginia Libraries, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Gate's Foundation, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - General Assembly, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - General Services, Department of, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Governor's Office, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Information Technology, Department of, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Information Technology Division, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Institute for Museum and Library Services, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Invitations, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Library Advisory Council (SCHEV), 2000. (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Library of Congress, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Library Development and Networking (LDN), 2000. (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Library Development and Networking (LDN), 2000. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Library Services Technology Advisory Council, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Locality Correspondence, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Personnel and Training, Department of, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Planning and Budget, Department of, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Proposed Legislation, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Publications and Educational Services Division, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Records Management and Imaging Services Division, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Richmond Area Museum Directors, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Southeastern Library Network, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - State - other, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - State Agencies - other, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - State Historical Records Advisory Board (SHRAB), 2000. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - State Networking and User Advisory Board (SNUAB), 2000. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - State Public Records Advisory Council, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Strategic Management Plan, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Coalition for Open Government, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Cultural Network, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Freedom of Information Advisory Council - regulatory, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Library Association, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 2001-2006 (Accession 43385)., 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes)
    This collection contains the correspondence of State Librarian, Nolan T. Yelich. Correspondents include but are not limited to; state and federal agencies, the library board and foundation, agency departments, associations, and foundations. Topics discussed are; Virginia State Library funding, collections and services. Included are; reports, letters, memorandums, and invitations.
    - Accomplishment Reports, 2003. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Agendas and Supporting Documentation, 2001-2006. (Box 1, Folder 2-8)
    - American Library Associatiation (ALA), 2001-2006. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Annual Reports, 2001-2006. (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
    - Archival and Information Services Division (AIS), 2001-2005. (Box 1, Folder 13-15)
    - Archives and Record Management Services Division, 2001-2006. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Art Museum of Western Virginia, 2001-2006. (Box 1, Folder 17-19)
    - Association for the Preservation of Virginia Antiquities (APVA), 2001-2006. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Association of Southeastern Research Libraries, 2001-2006. (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
    - Attorney General, 2001-2006. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Board Member Correspondence, 2001-2006. (Box 2, Folder 4-8)
    - Board Member Correspondence - Personal, 2001-2006. (Box 2, Folder 9-11)
    - Board Member - Miscellaneous, 2003-2006. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Board Minutes, 2001-2006. (Box 2, Folder 13-14)
    - Celebration 2007 (Jamestown-Yorktown), 2001-2006. (Box 2, Folder 15-17)
    - Center for Innovative Technology (Technology, Secretary of), 2004-2005. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Center for the Book, 2001-2006. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Chief Officers of State Library Agencies, 2001-2006. (Box 3, Folder 1-4)
    - Collection Management Services, 2001-2006. (Box 3, Folder 5-8)
    - Congress, 2001-2006. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Council of State Library Agencies in the Northeast, 2001-2005. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Council on America's First Freedom, 2001-2006. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Digital Library, 2001-2002. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Direct Constituent Correspondence, 2001-2006. (Box 3, Folder 13-15)
    - Education, Secretary of, 2001-2006. (Box 3, Folder 16-18)
    - Executive Aggreement, 2002-2003. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Federal Agencies, 2003. (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Finance and Administrative Services, 2001-2006. (Box 4, Folder 1-5)
    - Foundation Development Office, 2001-2006. (Box 4, Folder 6-13)
    - Freedom of Information Act, 2002-2006. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Freedom of Infromation Advisory Council, 2002-2006. (Box 5, Folder 1-4)
    - Friends of Virginia Libraries, 2001-2002. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Gates Foundation, 2001-2006. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Genealogical Societies, 2001-2006. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - General Assembly, 2001-2006. (Box 5, Folder 8-9)
    - General Services, Department of, 2001-2006. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Governor's Office, 2001-2006. (Box 5, Folder 11-18)
    - Information Technology, Department of, 2002. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Information Technology Services Division, 2001-2006. (Box 5, Folder 20-21)
    - Institute of Muesum and Library Services, 2001-2006. (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Invitations, 2001-2006. (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - Librarian Certification, 2004. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Library Advisory Council, 2001-2006. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Library Development and Networking Division, 2001-2006. (Box 6, Folder 5-12)
    - Library of Congress, 2001-2004. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Library Services and Construction Act, 2001-2006. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Locality Correspondence, 2001-2006. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - National Commission on Libraries and Information Science (NCLIS), 2002-2006. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Personnel and Training, Department of, 2001. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Planning and Budget, Department of, 2001-2004. (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Publications and Educational Services Division, 2001-2006. (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Records Management and Imaging Services Division, 2001-2006. (Box 7, Folder 1-5)
    - Richmond Area Museum Directors, 2001-2004. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - SIRS Databases, 2001; 2003. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Southeastern Library Network (SOLINET), 2001-2006. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Southern Council of State Library Agencies, 2006. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - States - Other, 2001-2006. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - State Agencies - Other, 2001-2006. (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
    - State Historical Records Advisory Board (SHRAB), 2001-2002. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - State Networking Users Advisory Board (SNUAB), 2001-2005. (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - State Public Records Advisory Council(SPRAC), 2001-2002. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Strategic Management Plan, 2001-2006. (Box 7, Folder 16-17)
    - Technology, Secretary of, 2001-2003. (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Coalition for Open Government, 2003-2006. (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Cultural Network, 2001-2006. (Box 7, Folder 20-21)
    - Virginia Freedom of Information Advisory Council, 2001. (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Virginia Library Association, 2001-2005. (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Public Library Directors Association, 2001-2006. (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - 2007 (Accession 44434)., .35 cu. ft. (1 box)
    This collection contains the correspondence of State Librarian, Nolan T. Yelich. Correspondents include but are not limited to; state and federal agencies, associations, and foundations. Topics discussed are; Virginia State Library funding, collections and services. Included are: reports, letters, memorandums, and invitations.
    - Agendas and Supporting Documentation, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Archival and Records Management Services, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Association of Southeastern Reseach Libraries (ASERL), 2007. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Board Members Correspondence, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Board Member Correspondence - personal, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Celebration 2007 (Jamestown-Yorktown), 2007. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Chief Officers of State Library Agences (COSLA), 2007. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Collections Management Services Division, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Education, Secretary of, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Federal Agencies, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Financial and Administrative Services Division, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Foundation Development Office, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA)Advisory Council, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Gates Foundation, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - General Assembly, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Government Correspondence - external, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Governor's Office, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Information Technology Services Division, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Institute of Museums and Library Services, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Invitations, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Library Board Minutes, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Library Development and Networking Division, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Locality Correspondence, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - National Commission on Libraries and Information Science (NCLIS), 2007. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Publications and Educational Services Division, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Research and Information Services, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Southern Council of State Library Agencies, Inc., 2007. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - State Agencies - other, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Strategic Management Plan, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Virginia Public Library Directors Association, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 30)
- 2007-2024 (Accession 54082)., 14.35 cu. ft. (41 boxes)
  Accession 54082 contains the correspondence and subject files of State Librarian, Dr. Sandra G. Treadway, 2007-2024. Subseries have been designated for State Government; Federal Agencies; Internal Divisions; Reports; Constituents; Localities; Subject Files; Library Board; Other Board, Commission and Committee Records; Miscellaneous; and Associations. Topics may include: Virginia State Library funding, collections and services. Files may contain correspondence, board agendas and attachments, event files, invitations, legislation, memoranda, minutes, programs and reports.
  Arranged according to an internal numerical filing system. Original order has been maintained.
  - Virginia State Government.